[Music]
[Música]
Okay families good afternoon today
bueno familias buenas tardes hoy está la
things are on fire we had to open the
cosa que arde hemos tenido que abrir el
live almost without desire as a family it's that
directo casi sin ganas en familia es que
today I opened live just to open because it's that I
hoy he abierto directo por abrir porque
barely had a topic of what you
es que no tenía tema apenas de los que
talk about okay given with him there I had an
hablas vale dado para con él allí lo
incredible time with you thank you very much
pasé increíble con ustedes muchísimas
one of the extracts you can't
gracias uno de los extractos no lo
see it here on this channel yet
podéis ver aquí en este canal todavía
[Music]
[Música]
could it be the end of spiderman
podrá ser el fin del hombre araña a
really to stop and not see the chocada
verdad para parar y no verlo del chocada
so as not to see it catches me a little lazy
para que no ver me pilla un poco vago
but it would give Dino to see
pero daría para dino ver
a doctor very welcome welcome
un doctor muy bienvenido bienvenido
well stable at the headquarters fixed member
bueno estable en la sede miembro fijado
today would be a good day to break a record
hoy sería un buen día para romper récord
or will it be kept in account in the chat but I
o se dejará en cuenta en el chat pero
want you to answer me and without joking around
quiero que me responda y sin cachondeo
okay sincerely answer
vale sinceramente responde con
sincerely to I am the chocas see I am
sinceridad a soy el chocas ve soy
kids okay very important to
chavalería vale muy importante a todo el
everyone who is arriving at this channel that
mundo que esté llegando a este canal que
you subscribe because here well here
os suscribas porque aquí bueno aquí
all things happen you saw how
pasan todas las cosas vieron cómo pasan
things happen here abraham welcome to the
las cosas aquí abraham bienvenido a la
family look how things happen
familia fijaros cómo pasan las cosas
here that yesterday suddenly it was a trend
aquí que ayer de repente fue tendencia
yesterday suddenly it was a worldwide trend
ayer de repente fue tendencia mundial
because we are talking about little things the
porque estamos hablando de poca cosa
whole internet is  speaking in fact right
todo internet está hablando de hecho
now it is my mother of beautiful love
ahora mismo es madre mía del amor
javitxu but that has happened in a few
javitxu pero que ha sucedido en pocos
moments I leave it that it is really is so so
instantes lo dejo que es realmente es
so serious and his relief and
tan tan tan grave y su desahogo y
contained pressure and what willy was serious
presión contenidas y lo de willy grave
was necessary what he crashed is serious
era necesario lo de choca es graves
rodrigo thanks for renewing the
rodrigo gracias por renovar lo del
crash is very serious not only because
choque es muy grave no solamente porque
that is his tendency to expand
esa es su tendencia el ampliar en
live is a little embarrassing it is not the
directo es un poco vergonzoso no es el
fact in itself it is not the fact in itself that he
hecho en sí no es el hecho en sí de que
has multiple accounts for out of the arse
tenga multi cuentas para out of el arse
also that is embarrassing
asimismo que eso es vergonzoso
soledad kirin that can give you how
soledad kirin que te puede dar qué
embarrassed I mean myself throwing myself out by
vergüenza o sea yo mismo echando me piro
myself I mean how embarrassing me with
por mí mismo o sea qué vergüenza yo con
a multiple account throwing myself out but
una multi cuenta echándome pero pues a
myself is not only that it is that in
mí mismo no solamente es eso es que en
those multiple accounts and now we are going to
esas multi cuentas y ahora lo vamos a
see today's live in several
ver el directo de hoy en en varios
extracts that is why it is important that you
extractos por eso es importante que os
subscribe to this channel click the
suscribas a este canal
subscribe button which is
darle al botón de suscribir que es
completely free
completamente gratuito
this is the channel of the salseros they fixed
este es el canal de los salseros fijaron
the importance of this salcé channel or
la importancia de este canal de salcé o
that of all the multiple accounts that yesterday
que de todas las multi cuentas que ayer
went viral worldwide everyone
fueron virales mundialmente todo el
is talking about this  right now it turns out
mundo está hablando de esto ahora mismo
that it comes out here in the middle of
resulta ser que sale aquí en pleno
live and I had to throw myself to the ground
directo y me tuve que tirar al suelo
because I had to throw myself to the ground
porque me tuve que tirar al suelo
thanks bad donettes for the prime
gracias mal donettes por el prime
that one of those secondary accounts that
que una de esas cuentas secundarias que
Chocas has on Twitter is dedicated to the
tiene en twitter el chocas está dedicada
king of salsa
al rey del salsero
Chocas is so angry with
el chocas le arde tanto los vídeos de
Javi Oliveira's videos that he created a multi
javi oliveira que se creó una multi
account with a picture of a Russian
cuenta con una foto de un ruso
to answer me because he can't
para contestarme porque no puede
answer me from his own account okay those
contestarme desde su cuenta vale ya esos
tremendous ones I don't know how we manage
tremendos no sé cómo nos las apañamos
but we always have a certain
pero nosotros siempre tenemos cierto
role in all the salseros in all the
papel en todos los salseros en todos los
bathrooms we have a certain role dallas and
aseos tenemos cierto papel dallas y
willy right now we'll see it is what they
willy ahora mismo lo veremos es lo que
write on twitter face we're going to see it
escriben en twitter cara lo vamos a ver
here Eliazar welcome welcome
aquí eliázar bienvenido bienvenido
friends welcome friend okay not
amigos bienvenido amigo vale ya no
only self-fellatio
solamente la auto felación
self-fellatio okay yes that you can be
auto felación vale que sí que te pueda
ashamed that not doing yourself there is a
vergüenza que no haciéndote tú hay una
suck off to yourself that he manages to give us
[__] a ti mismo que consigue a darnos
not only that
ya no solamente eso
here the move
aquí la movida
here the move is that
aquí la movida es qué
Chocas from those accounts has
el choca desde esas cuentas ha
shown his true self the excuse
demostrado su verdadero ser ya la excusa
of the people of the chocaros not of the
de la gente de los choqueros no de la
toxic community of Chocas the excuse of
comunidad tóxica del choque la excusa de
not  it's that his character is the role he
no es que su personaje es que es el rol
plays not the role of protecting
que interpreta no el rol de proteger de
Catí VIP and that has been a good
catí vip y eso sí que ha sido un buen
role that he didn't even play in Marbella Vice
rol que ni en marbella vice lo
okay now we've
interpretó vale ya es que hemos
discovered the real chocas insults
descubierto el verdadero chocas insultos
about the physique
por el físico
oh you and that I knew a little bit of
ay tú y que yo conociera un poco de
bullying
bullying
Manel
manel
and insults to women and insults very
e insultos a mujeres e insultos muy
disgusting the
asqueroso los
insults very very very very disgusting
insultos muy muy muy muy asquerosos
thank you very much fever for renewing but you
muchas gracias fever por renovar pero
know what's the worst and this until
sabéis que es lo peor y esto hasta que
months or years go by I won't be
vaya pasando meses incluso años no lo
able to say it but it
podré decir pero que yo
was very funny because there's a tweet in
fue muy gracioso porque hay un tuit en
which I was
el que yo el año pasado le estoy
answering one of his multiple ones is
contestando a una de sus múltiples está
saying it seems to me a very
diciendo me parece una cuenta muy
suspicious account because it's only you you
sospechosa porque está solamente tú te
have on the choca I don't know what tricks
has sobre el choca no sé qué trucos
thank you very much for that prime
muchas gracias por ese prime
okay there's a tweet from last year but there
vale hay un tuit del año pasado pero es
's more
que hay más
with time or being able to tell something that has been
con el tiempo o poder contar algo que a
happening to me and it's going to be
mí me ha estado pasando y va a ser
outrageous and it's going to be a scandal
indignante y va a ser un escándalo
of other people that I have seen
de otra gente a la que yo he visto
clues let's go clues very shameless
indicios vamos indicios descaradísimo
download edition because here people
descarga edición porque aquí la gente se
believe that you have to be a fortune teller  to
cree que tienes que ser adivino para
realize what you have to have
darte cuenta lo que tienes que tener
what I tell you I have accused me of anything goes
qué te digo yo me han acusado de todo
but then you and the management plus this plus this plus
vale pero luego tú y la gestión más esto
this and says take two plus
más esto más esto y dice toma dos más
two equals four I
dos son cuatro
can't tell it now Sofia and you will
no puedo contarlo ahora sofía y ya lo
understand when the months or
entenderéis cuando pasen los meses o
even years pass you will understand but there are
incluso años lo entenderéis pero es que
people that I have a lot of the indication
hay gente que yo tengo mucho el indicio
that do the same or worse or worse but I
que hace lo mismo o peor o peor pero yo
am saving it saved because what he
voy guardando guardado porque lo que
said and vice of the socas tremendous click
dijo y vice del socas tremendo clic
eleazar commands at least in the group of
eleazar manda al menos en el grupo de
kids and we see it we are going to see
chavalería y lo vemos lo vamos a ver
anything goes but there are many things there are
todo vale pero que hay muchas cosas hay
many people who do that and not one or two
mucha gente que hace eso y no uno ni dos
many people who do it insult because they do
mucha gente que lo hace insultar porque
not have the balls to say the good thing
no tienen [__] de decir lo bueno
because they do not have the balls if that
porque no tienen [__] si eso lo
first because they do not have the balls or
primero porque no tienen [__] o por
why or why not because he remains a
qué o por qué no porque se queda sea
victim or for anything okay it
víctima o por cualquier cosa vale
seems regrettable
parece lamentable
thank you very much that then they have been
muchas gracias que luego se han estado
messing with him
metiendo con él
because he has made the same insults
porque las ha hecho los mismos insultos
because they are at the same level to me that
porque están al mismo nivel a mí que no
nobody comes to me now yes that the
me venga nadie ahora de sí que lo del
Dallas was at another level that I
dallas estaba a otro nivel que yo
criticized it he wanted  dallas in the
critiqué lo quiso el dallas en el
sense that I understand his outburst
sentido de que entiendo su desahogo
but
pero
bah I
bah
think what he did is terrible because in the
me parece fatal lo que hizo porque al
end you put yourself on the same level you don't
final te pones al mismo nivel no te
put yourself on the same level no matter how much you think about it you have to be
pones al mismo nivel por mucho que lo
clear and say what you
hay que ser claro y decir lo que uno
think if not it's not false seriously but there are
piensa si no es falso serio pero si hay
things that you can't be so so so
cosas que tampoco puede ser tan tan tan
transparent no because in the end you
transparente no porque al final te
can damage yourself your image it's
puedes perjudicar a ti tu imagen es
simply because of that and also there were people who did
simplemente por eso y además había gente
n't know there were people who maybe such
que no se había gente que a lo mejor tal
but it's that gives things
pero es que da las cosas
dallas said much worse things a dick a
dallas dijo cosas mucho peores una [__]
dick a dick
una [__] una [__]
last night we were tweets we were
anoche estuvimos tweets estuvimos
reading his tweets it clashes in the multi
leyendo tweets de él choca en las multi
accounts
cuentas
in info you have the ibai thing 48,000 ago praise well okay
en info tienes lo de ibai hace 48.000
pilar let's see it a
loa pues vale pilar lo vamos a ver una
dick whoever says that the twitter
[__] el que diga que el los twitter
clashes what we were reading yesterday that I
choca que estuvimos leyendo ayer que
think here we're going to see a few there are no
creo aquí vamos a ver unos cuantos no
things on the same level a dick
hay cosas al mismo nivel una [__]
on the contrary once we're at it at
al contrario ya puestos ya puestos por
least dallas has balls of steel
lo menos da la tiene los huevos de acero
from his account
de su cuenta
once we're at it once
ya puestos
what happens is that it's the
ya puestos lo que pasa es que es el
clash
choque
and the other is dallas of course I do
y el otro es el dallas claro
n't support one thing or the other  another one
que no apoyo ni una cosa ni la otra
that does not support one thing or the other let it be
que no apoya ni una cosa ni la otra
clear
que quede claro
that they do not support one thing or the other but
que no apoyen una cosa ni la otra pero
that we have to be hypocrites to
que hay que ser hipócritas para
justify this clashing
justificar esto del chocar
okay
vale
incredible
increíble
let's see some let's not see
vamos a ver algunas no vamos a ver
some of the things look here you have the
algunas de las cosas mira aquí tenéis la
tremendous thing is that here on the internet it is not who it is who
tremenda es que aquí en internet no es
and once again it is demonstrated but this is that
y una vez más se demuestra pero es que
this is incredible
es que esto es increíble
is that this is incredible because this is
es que esto es increíble porque esto es
once again even Javi Oliveira is
una vez más hasta javi oliveira tiene
right
razón
this is once again even Javi Oliveira
esto es una vez más hasta javi oliveira
is right
tiene razón
and the hypocrisy of the internet me and the
y la hipocresía de internet yo y la
hypocrisy of the internet [ __ ] do you want to
hipocresía de internet [__] quieres
insult someone who has insulted you
insultar a alguien que te ha insultado
I have done it with the everyday ways
yo lo he hecho con las formas de
with the kilo when I enjoy myself with
con el kilo cuando me disfruto a mí con
people who enjoy half alone returned
gente que disfruta medio solo devuelto
that then the clinicians see since it was to do that
que luego ven los clínicos ya que fue
okay but do it from your [ __ ] account
vale pero hazlo desde tu [__] cuenta
do it with your [ __ ] account
hazlo con tu [__] cuenta
you said that in a year his
dijiste que en un año se le acaba el
deal will be over look now the king did it
chollo mira ahora el rey lo hizo de
again man let's see I sincerely do not
nuevo hombre a ver yo sinceramente no le
wish evil on anyone since I was
deseo el mal a nadie ya que iba
defended I have already seen it  uploaded and
defendido ya lo he visto lo subido y
here since he said it's very
aquí ya que ha dicho como que es muy
normal for them to do that that everyone
normal que hagan eso que que todo el
has it, well I don't have it and
mundo lo tiene pues yo no lo tengo y
here I don't have it, you have
aquí yo no lo tengo yo a mi me habéis
seen me here on occasion with other
visto aquí en alguna ocasión con otras
accounts that they have left me but for
cuentas que me han dejado pero para
other matters that
otros asuntos
are matters that are also legal they
que son asuntos que además son legales
are legal because I also have the
son legales porque además tengo la
proof that they give me today it is a habit
prueba de que me dan de hoy es hábito
more you want me to have this account
más quieres que tengo esta cuenta
you want me to leave it and let me
quieres que te la dejes y déjame la
take it good field and it was to certify
tomas buen campo y era para certificar
some tweets
unos tweets
but you know what it is when I can
pero sabéis que es que cuando pueda
tell the thing when the heretic grg passes
contar la cosa cuando pase el hereje grg
every month he makes me renew by hand
todos los meses me hace renovar a mano
doctor groups renew sámano friends
doctor grupos renueva sámano amigos
verse king but you know what is the
verso rey pero es que sabéis que es lo
worst when I can tell when
peor cuando pueda contar cuando pase el
time passes I am going to I am going to tell you more
tiempo os voy a os voy a contar más
right now we are going to focus on those
ahora mismo nos vamos a centrar a los
of the txoko
del txoko
but when time passes the months
pero cuando pase el tiempo los meses
years I don't know how much will pass to be able to tell
años no sé cuánto pasará a poder contar
more because this is going to be a scandal
más porque esto va a ser un escándalo el
this issue of accounts and of the people who
tema este de cuentas y de la gente que
have done this is going to be a point
has hecho esto va a ser un punto
scandal
escándalo
because social networks do nothing
porque las redes sociales no hacen nada
and they go unpunished and you are going to freak out and  you're going to
y son impunes y vais a flipar y vais a
freak out
flipar
now you can tell now you can tell but
ya puede contar ya poder contar pero
you're going to freak out because this guy
vais a flipar porque esto que un tío se
can create eight accounts to call
pueda crear ocho cuentas para llamar de
everyone else anything do it with your [ __ ]
todo a los demás hazlo con tu [__]
account say it from your [ __ ] account and whoever has
cuenta dilo desde tu [__] cuenta y el
any problem that can
que tenga algún problema que te pueda
sue you stop thank you very much honey
demandar me para muchas gracias cariño
but that a guy can do this
pero que un tío se se pueda hacer esto
is because the networks don't ask you for your [ __ ] ID
es porque las redes no te piden el [__]
what is this about allowing anonymity on
qué es esto de permitir el anonimato en
the networks
las redes
whoever doesn't want it whoever wants to be anonymous can be anonymous whoever
el que no quiera el que quiera ser
wants to be anonymous can
el que quiera ser anónimo que lo sea que
be anonymous
sea anónimo
but they can't start insulting someone
pero que no pueda ponerse a insultar a
else
otro
because when you walk down the street you ca
a que ustedes cuando vais por la calle
n't just go and punch
no podéis [__] y darle un puñetazo a
a person who's walking by
una persona que vaya por ahí
without someone stopping us or knowing who I am
sin que alguien nos detenga o sepa quién
because the internet is possible
soy pues porque el internet si se puede
[Music]
[Música]
and these big companies go unpunished and I'll
y estas empresas grandes son impunes y
tell you the scandal
ya os contaré el escándalo
when I can
cuando pueda
but the thing is that this shouldn't be
pero es que esto no se debería poder
allowed that with anonymity you want
permitir que con anonimato tú quieres
anonymity then don't participate in the
anonimato pues no participes en los
chalets the things
chalets las cosas
you want anonymity don't participate in
tú quieres anonimatos no participes en
the chats that don't  you can insult that you
los chats que no puedas insultar que no
cannot criticize that you cannot
puedas criticar que no puedas
belittle disqualify
menospreciar descalificar
but I blame the high
pero echo la culpa lo tienen los altos
officials those in charge and things you
cargos los responsables y las cosas
are exaggerating xavi I will be able to
estás exagerando xavi ya os podré
find you I will be able to tell you I will be able to
encontrar ya os podré contar ya os podré
tell you if I am exaggerating remember
contar si estoy exagerando nos acuérdate
that one year one year proves you right with this
que el año un año da la razón con esto
thank you very much
muchísimas gracias
and they
y
tell it on the other hand
lo cuentan por otro lado
man
hombre
man look at the caught look how his
hombre mira la pillada mira cómo se le
face breaks down bando they catch him for
descompone la cara bando lo pillan por
him
él
there he is with his cat the
ahí está con su cat
Harper issue
el tema de harper
javi oliveira was right genius man
javi oliveira tenía razón genio hombre
gamer pad multi storytellers and there was
almohadilla gamer multi cuenteros y
always has well these are
siempre había tiene bueno estas son
deleted accounts deleted these are
cuentas borradas borradas estas son
accounts the owner which is the one from hubei is the one
cuenta la dueño que es la de hubei es la
dedicated to me the one from eugenio is
que me tiene dedicada a mí la de eugenio
dedicated to me but look at
me la dedica a mí pero es que fíjate tú
how things are with the passing of the
cómo son las cosas con el paso de los
years
años
with the passing of the years
con el paso de los años
notice how many people insult me ​​well on the
fijaros cuánta gente me insulta bien
internet I mean I usually pass I
internet o sea yo suelo pasar yo a mí me
get the insults on twitter on
llegan los insultos en twitter en
youtube whatever and what I usually
youtube lo que sea y yo lo que suelo
do is if it is very serious report pin
hacer es si es muy grave reportar pin
pin without I'm going to go see report  there are
pin sin voy a ir a ver reportar hay
times that it is even with the tweet with
veces que es incluso es con el tuit con
my click be it a thing that I use
el clic mío sea una cosa que utilice
wrote to criticize me okay but another
escribió para criticarme vale pero otra
thing that you use my click to
cosa que tú utilices clic mío para
defame me it's worth it he took it down appeal friend
difamar me vale lo tumbó apela amigo
appeal to what twitter will already give you the
apela a lo que ya twitter te dará la
reason it's not
razón no
worth it but each end with the people who
vale pero cada final con la gente que me
insult me ​​that I say when I get
insulta que lo digo yo cuando me llega
an insult by I usually block report
un insulto por suelo bloquear reportar
idea twitter you can see that they suffer from their
idea twitter puede verse que sufren de
account their accounts of no no but they fixed
cuenta sus cuentas de no no pero fijaron
so that I of all the people who
para que yo de toda la gente que me
insult me ​​who give me [ __ ] at the end
insulta que me pone gilipolleces al cabo
of the day I
del día
stayed with this account that I watched a
me quedé con esta cuenta que yo veía un
tv said me me young handsome I didn't start
tv decía yo yo joven guapo yo no me puse
looking that it was an account of a Russian model
a buscar que era una cuenta de un modelo
but I said
pero yo decía
eugenio this one comes for her he's going to put her to
eugenio este viene a por la va a poner a
touch me he supports her with the crash but
tocarme la apoya con el choque pero
even in videos where you don't have your
incluso en vídeos que no tienes la
head with him you crash okay
cabeza con él chocas vale esto lo
you can see this in today's video on the
podréis ver en el vídeo de hoy del canal
main channel okay in the video that I upload now
principal vale en el vídeo que subo ya
the main face you can see this the
la cara principal podéis ver esto la
story with neuer with eugenio he
historia con neuer con eugenio se
appeared at every moment such and I see
aparecía a cada momento tal y yo vemos
that abba would not have been  0 I didn't think it
que abba no hubiese ser 0 no pensaba que
was him Chose I thought it was someone from
era él choca creía que era alguien del
Chose
chocas
or someone from Chose someone close to
o alguien del choque alguien cercana al
Chose a really big Chose fan very
chocar un fan del choca muy pesado muy
obsessed with Chose or even
obsesionado en el choca o incluso
some fan of mine but who was a bigger
algún fan mío pero que fuera más fan del
Chose fan and because they were family that I
choca y que por ser familia que yo
knew he didn't have the balls to
conociera no tenía los [__] de
put it on his own account but it was something strange it
ponerlo de su cuenta pero era algo raro
was remembering or rather a
es que era recordar o sea una cuenta
newly created account that only tweeted
recién creada que solamente tuiteaba
to play it I supported it the point Chose
para tocar me la apoyaba el punto choca
that I did a live me talking about
que hacía un directo yo hablando sobre
the win bicho dubbing and I came and started
el doblaje win [__] y venía y me ponía
watching already 3,000 viewers and Chose
a mirar ya 3.000 espectadores y él choca
has nine thousand
tiene nueve mil
and we didn't realize this family and we did
y no nos dimos cuenta de esto familia y
n't realize these two face
no nos dimos cuenta de estos dos cara
because the night tell it I would report it I would
porque la noche cuéntalo reportaría lo
block it and even understands me but we didn't
bloquearía y hasta me entiende pero no
realize this detail man
nos dimos cuenta de este detalle tío
and there were people who follow there were people who
y había gente que sigue había gente que
were commenting on this
estaba comentando esto
we didn't realize this man
no nos dimos cuenta de esto tío
here we would have shined
aquí lo hubiéramos brillado el año
last year time last year we
pasado tiempo el mismísimo año pasado le
would have caught this
hubiéramos pillado esto
the guy has the need
el tío tiene la necesidad
to see that I have the greatest with the majority
de ver que tengo la mayor con la mayoría
of negative comments than positive
de comentarios negativos que positivos
in the video that I made to  look at how much
en el vídeo que le hice a fíjate tú si
my video hurt his ego
le dolió en el ego mi vídeo
that he needs to check my
que tiene la necesidad de revisar mis
comments a guy with 40,000
comentarios un tío con 40.000 subs de
paid subs or tweets that I wish I had
pagos o en tweets que ojalá lo tuviera
40 thousand paid subs this reminded me of
40 mil sus de pago esto me recordó a
when you caught Dallas using the
cuando pillaste al dallas usando la
full full account to insult
cuenta de full full para insultar a la
people yeah well but when it comes to light it
peña sí bueno pero eso salga a la luz
wasn't just him
que no solamente era él
mayo didn't ask for it it
a mayo no lo pidió
's an account that 3 of them had
es una cuenta que tenían entre 3 por lo
apparently and he would put some things on someone else and
visto y algunas cosas las ponía a otro y
others on someone else and that's it well let's see
otras a poner a otro y eso bueno a ver
just like you imposed each one he
igual que tú impuso a cada uno le
lent his own from choca solo okay
prestó suyo del choca solo vale
even though he works more than 12 hours a day
aunque crimea más de 12 horas al día
goodbye
adiós
the money he earns will come what a
llegará el dineral que gana
complex he has guys I already said it
que de complejo tiene tíos ya lo dije
yesterday and I'll say it at the end of my video
ayer y lo digo al final de mi vídeo
choca you are a failure you
chocas eres un fracasado
only have money you
solo tienes dinero
only have money
sólo tiene dinero
the treasures that I have and the family
los tesoros que tengo yo y la familia
that I have I don't have it study because
que tengo yo no la tiene estudio porque
you when more than 12 hours of
tú cuando terminan más de 12 horas de
string trio that make your life on the
string trío que te hacen la vida en el
computer are over you are a big brother making your
ordenador eres un gran hermano hacer la
life live dude you're going to  see what they
vida en directo tío te vas a ver qué
think of you and he dedicates a lot of time to it
opinan de ti y le dedica mucho tiempo
man because really imagine how many
tío porque realmente imaginaros cuantas
hours you dedicate to this
horas dedicas en esto
how many hours he dedicates to this god
cuántas horas dedica a esto dios
[ __ ] it seems [ __ ] great to me to
[__] a mí me parece de [__] madre de
work 12 hours I have worked 12 hours
trabajar 12 horas yo la he trabajado 12
surely I worked 12 hours
horas seguramente yo trabajé 12 horas
also outside of live between live shows
también fuera de directo entre directos
that could be 5 hours a day or 6 and
que puedan ser 5 horas al día o 6 y
then the videos that I record and TV to the CEO
luego los videos que grabó y teles al
and so on I surely also put in
ceo y demás seguramente yo eché también
12 hours but the rest I'm taking advantage of
12 horas pero el resto voy aprovechando
this with my wife and my father well I know it
esto con mi mujer ya mi padre bueno sé
takes me a while I don't know how much but
que me va un rato me no sé cuánto pero
the clash he dedicates a lot of time he has
el choque le dedica un montón de tiempo
made time
ha hecho tiempo
to invent personalities invent
a inventarse personalidades a inventarse
names well look at you I mean this has to be
nombres pues fíjate tú o sea esto tiene
good this account is not
que ponerle buena esta cuenta no está
confirmed what they have are indications
confirmada lo que tienen son indicios
some of the accounts that are
algunas de las cuentas que están
saying here
diciendo aquí
confirmed is Eugenio's and
confirmada está la de eugenio y la de
Katy's that almost nobody is talking about by the
katy que no está hablando casi nadie por
way
cierto
Abelardo went viral a bit when
abelardo se viraliza un poco cuando
I took out the video and from the main channel
saqué yo el vídeo y del canal principal
and now we'll see when we finish the
y ahora vemos lo cuando terminemos el
clash we'll see about Willy do you think you're
choque ya vemos lo de willy te crees
calm today we have here  for charata it
tranquilo hoy tenemos aquí para charata
comes out well
sale bien
[Music]
[Música]
you need help you don't go to
necesitas ayuda a ti tampoco te pases a
raúl
raúl
[Music]
[Música]
well that needs help maybe
bueno que necesita ayuda puede ser
but let's not grab this because
pero que no vayamos a agarrar esto a que
this is like I've seen on twitter no that there
esto es como he visto en twitter no que
are people saying
hay gente diciendo las enfermedades
mental illnesses I don't know what I don't know how many no don't
mentales no sé qué no sé cuántos no
piss me off you've been a year
no me toquéis los huevos lleváis un año
and a half you've been
y medio
applauding for a year and a half something that's not only
aplaudiendo una cosa que no solamente
critical
crítica
interrupting you javi but the anime willy
interrumpirte javi pero el anime willy
ref is right now
ref está en estos mismos instantes al
red hot includes copy paste asses yes
rojo vivo incluye culos copypaste si
accusations of high serious speeds calm down calm down
acusaciones de altas velocidades graves
let's watch it
tranquilo tranquilo vamos a verlo
too of course calm down calm down calmly do
también por supuesto
n't worry it's
calma con calma no preocupéis
not justifiable in family thanks
no es justificable en familia gracias
welcome you've been here you've been here for
bienvenidos habéis estado habéis estado
a year and I'm not saying it for my people okay
un año y no lo digo por mi gente vale
but you've been here for a year that people
pero habéis estado un año que personas
with total the and that with total head not
con total los y que con total cabeza no
only me because there I am a channel of
solamente yo porque hay soy un canal de
salt I know or how disgusting no that they only criticize
sal se o qué asco no que sólo critican
no people like me one trio
no gente como yo one trío
thank goodness that someone dear like them
menos mal que alguien querido como ellos
also said that it didn't seem right to him
también lo dijo que no le parecía bien
neither role nor character nor [ __ ]
ni papel ni personaje ni pollas
my  role or character or dicks dude
mi papel ni personaje ni pollas tío
you applauded like it's funny
habéis aplaudido como una gracia
that a guy
que un tío
starts insulting with impunity dude that
se ponga a insultar impunemente tío que
even almost all of the videos we have
incluso casi todos los vídeos que
reacting to his stuff I've had to
tenemos reaccionando a cosas suya los he
delete because they put an
tenido que eliminar porque me ponen
age restriction on the language he
restricción de edad de la del lenguaje
uses
que utiliza
come on man
venga ya hombre
all of you who are criticizing now
todos los que estáis criticando ahora
done
hecho
many
muchos
many you have applauded for a
muchos lo habéis aplaudido durante un
year
año
god what how bad this is I don't know if they are
dios qué qué mal esto no sé si son
confirmed accounts well these are
cuentas confirmadas bueno estos son
light
light
from this katyn's account or in case
desde la cuenta de esta de katyn o por
you're interested in what she commented about
si te interesa lo que ha comentado lo de
socas she gets quite wet red heart
socas se moja bastante corazón rojo
ballet edu thank you very much guys those of you who
ballet edu muchísimas gracias chicos los
are in the kids' group
que estáis en el grupo de chavalería
info to keep track of the weather send it
info para ir cogiendo clima lo mandáis
in the dm and we'll react now
en el md y lo vamos reaccionando ahora
okay extract by extract let's see these
vale extracto por extracto a ver estos
online to girls no well they are
online a chicas no bueno son chicas
obviously older girls well
mayores evidentemente a bueno
well neither let's go in let's
bueno tampoco tampoco entremos en
see
a ver
because he doesn't have to know the ages
porque no tiene por qué saber las edades
or anything like that
ni demás
here someone catches him the crash has
aquí le pilla alguien el choque ha
covered up rather look here he asks
encubierto más bien mira aquí le pide a
someone because he directly blocks
alguien porque bloquea directamente a
this one and says the crash covered up
este y le dice el chocas encubierto más
rather and says he is  meaning
bien y dice él está queriendo decir que
if you crash hahahahaha I hope so and if he wins I
si chocas jajajajaja ojalá sí y si gana
know what he wins and he's going to be talking
se lo que él gana y va a estar hablando
here with you
aquí contigo
the only thing he has is me
lo único que tiene es yo
this girl is two days away from turning 18
esta chica tienen dos días de cumplir 18
javi okay dude that's why I'm telling you let's not
javi vale tío por eso te digo no
get into it either
entremos ya tampoco
[ __ ] it would be the best to get into that
[__] ya sería la [__] entrar en esas
stuff okay they already support each other
cosas vale
all that stuff name that
ya se apoyan todas esas cosas nombre eso
seems too much to me look here for
ya me parece demasiado mira aquí por
example they have another account but this is
ejemplo tienen otra cuenta pero esto en
based on the fact that sometimes the way of
base a que a veces que la forma de
writing is the same dude the same thing happened to me
escribir la misma tío a mí me pasó igual
with a person who thinks that I
con una persona que se cree que que yo
have
tengo
some psychic who reads your mind and
algún vidente que te lee la mente y te
asks you for the multiple accounts or that I have no no
pide a la multi cuentas o que yo tengo
no friends the same way of
no no no amigos la misma forma de
writing you comment on things that only
escribir comentas cosas que solamente
the person in question can know the
puede saber la persona protagonista las
same screenshots the timing I mean these
mismas capturas de pantalla lo timing o
are things that are crazy no
sea son cosas que flipas no
look here answer from eugenio they left the
mira aquí contesta de eugenio dejaron
public burned it's that absolutely
público ardido es que absolutamente
everyone laughs at you and tells you that you are
todos se ríen de ti y te digan que eres
pitiful so if you are really burned
lamentable entonces si estás bien ardido
this is referring to my video well yes
esto es referente a mi vídeo es pues si
you are burned dude well
que estás ardido tío
yes you are burned you crash dude that
pues sí que estás ardido chocas tío que
not only you  you ate my live streams in
no solamente te comiste mis directos en
my video with chips but you ate
mi vídeo con papitas sino que te comiste
my video share with chips you
mi vídeo compartir con papitas te
ate my video you ate
comiste mi vídeo te comiste
the comments if you came in from time to
los comentarios si entrabas de vez en
time the comments of what
cuando los comentarios de que decía la
people said well of course a lot of people are going to
gente pues claro que mucha gente me va a
enjoy me without fashion restrictions and I had
disfrutar sin trabas de moda y tenía
a lot more audience than me but
muchísima más audiencia que yo pero
infinitely
infinitamente
and now here it counts alternately xd but
y ahora aquí se cuenta alterna xd pero
if two months before it went viral I already
si hace dos meses antes de lo viral ya
had 5,000 subscribers and a peak of
tenía 5000 de suscriptores y un pico de
7,000 beavers and an average of 34 thousand
7000 beavers y una media de 34 mil
strings like nobody else is that
string como que nadie otra cosa es que
the viral made more people know about it
lo viral hizo que lo conociera más gente
but to say that he was nobody with
eso sí pero decir que no era nadie con
that number is to throw away many more
esa cifra es tirar a muchos más
with 5,000 subscribers you are already in the
con 5000 de suscriptores ya estás en el
top 20 in Spain and handle an average of
top 20 de españa y manejar una media de
5 thousand views much more but the point
5 mil visuales mucho más pero el punto
was to comment that he did not know
era que comentarse que no conocía a
anyone and just look at christine and nigrán
nadie y sólo mira christine y nigrán
well known and great and just recently
conocida y genial y recién hace poco
reached 5,000 of his family
alcanzó 5000 de su familia
he chocas says that we are
el chocas dice que nosotros no somos
nobody because we do not have 5,000 of his there are
nadie porque no tenemos 5.000 de sus hay
here  right now
aquí ahora mismo
2700 people
2700 personas
appreciate it if anyone can if I can't it's
le agradecería a quien pueda es que no
okay but we have a button
pueda no pasa nada pero tenemos un botón
a member level that's only worth 0
un nivel de miembro que solamente vale 0
with 90
con 90
notice an idiot how many videos will he
aviso un [__] cuantos vídeos de baja
dedicate a silly thing a lot for
dedicará una tontería muchísimo para
a lot they go but come on a lot it wouldn't
muchísimos van pero vamos muchísimo no
even be how much I have
sería ni cuánto llevo
if I were you I would leave the
si yo fuera tú dejaría el extracto del
Choca extract for later because Will is
choca para más tarde porque will está
spitting fire so much it's good let's take
escupiendo fuego tanto es bueno haber
a break now and we'll go to
vamos a hacer ahora una pausa y vamos a
Will's and finish this extract and
lo de will y termino este extracto y
we're going to take a break from the hand of
vamos a hacer una pausa de la mano de
Willy
willy
Geim Pacino well that's already part of the
geim pacino bueno eso ya parte de los
members apart from the members
miembros a parte de los miembros
apart from the titles
a parte de los títulos
[Music]
[Música]
that can't leave on Prime if you have
que no puede dejar en prime si tenéis el
Amazon stop and okay if not the money is
amazon para y vale que si no el dinero
only left the PSOE save it thank you very much thank you very much
sólo queda el psoe se guarde muchísimas
for being
gracias gracias muchas gracias por hacer
members
de miembros
thank you very much I'm
muchísimas gracias
not talking about Choca then send it to me
no hablo de choca pues mandarme lo
in the group too please
también en el grupo por favor
Emilio thank you very much
emilio muchísimas gracias muchísimas
thank you very much please all of you who are not
gracias por favor todos los que no seáis
Choca make the members okay right
el choca hacer los miembros vale razón
welcome to the family uncle welcome to
bienvenido a la familia tío bienvenido a
the family of  sant is called you have a
la familia de sant se llama tienes una
photo of life a hug reason
foto de vida la un abrazo razón
Alejandro welcome welcome by
alejandro bienvenido bienvenido por
Alejandro renewing no no welcome welcome welcome
alejandro renovando no no bienvenido
to the so
bienvenido bienvenido a la tan
welcome can to the 90 cent ones are
bienvenida lata a los de 90 céntimos son
tin let's see how much Zlatan there is here and
de lata a ver cuánto zlatan hay aquí y
how many Spaniards
cuántos españoles
because my hand
porque mi mano
welcome I I don't know thanks for that
bienvenido yo yo no sé gracias por ese
prime let's
prime
see therefore it's about Grey and Willy
a ver por tanto es lo de grey y willy
well we finish this extract of the
bueno terminamos este extracto de las
multi accounts
multi cuentas
Javi don't see the response from Greece
javi no veas la respuesta de grecia en
live discouraged face she
directo cara desanimada
is sad I think today is a day
está triste creo hoy es un día muchas
thank you very much Gabi for the lawyer
gracias gabi para el abogado
for Ramón for Ramón
para ramón para ramón
look at this tour and this tour and it
fijaros en este tour y en este tour y me
seems to me a [ __ ] shame
parece una [__] vergüenza
for the one I'm saying that
para el que estoy diciendo que no está
the level of I don't know what this is worth I had a
el nivel de no sé qué vale este tuve una
[ __ ] shame okay
[__] vergüenza vale
Gonzalo a man with his son okay
gonzalo un hombre con su hijo vale
and Luna says the love for his bonus who will be
y dice luna el amor por su bono que será
the woman and the crash arrives and answers him
la mujer y llega el choque y le contesta
and he crashes and answers him hey Luna
y el chocas y le contesta oye luna
Michelle your husband is a stalker and a
michelle tu marido es un acosador y un
bastard I hope that when you stop him you
desgraciado espero que cuando lo dejes
miss these at 62
de menos estos al 62
and me too and I'm also super
y yo también y yo también estoy súper
happy today with these fake I'm super
feliz hoy con estos falseó estoy súper
happy I'm going with these since they are all
feliz voy con estos al ser todos son
topics that I like damn no aurum
temas que a mí me gustan [__] no aurum
play explode it to the house 8
play la explota a la casa 8
these are the [ __ ]
estos son los [__]
and watch out for him with the video of you think they're
y cuidado con él con el vídeo de crees
going to go
que te van ea
yeah
sí
and vegeta is reading william's tweets
y vegeta está leyendo los tweets de
live [ __ ] we're not going to make
william live [__] no vamos a dar
it we're
abastos
not going to make it today
no vamos a dar abasto hoy
or so serious the [ __ ] went up okay because I have to be
o sea grave subió el ojete vale por
careful with that okay okay okay okay okay okay we're
tengo que tener cuidado con eso vale
careful with this
vale vale vale tenemos cuidado con esto
okay the hour ander a hug queen thank you
vale la horita ander un abrazo reina
so much welcome you have
muchísimas gracias bienvenida la tenéis
the link pinned in the chat okay for
el enlace fijado en el chat vale para
those who want to become a member guys
los que quieran hacerse miembro chicos
this tweet
este tuit
this tweet is nonsense
este tuit es una burrada
a nonsense go to the wife of the man
una burrada irte a la mujer del hombre
who is putting yours about him about
que está poniendo en tuyo sobre el sobre
his baby
su bebé
to insult him and accuse him of a
para insultarle y para acusarle de
crime but why have more like this with a
delito pero por qué tener más así con un
stranger boy what's wrong with you how long has it been since you
desconocido chico qué te pasa cuánto
[ __ ] what a bitter girl there are
lleva sin [__] menuda amargada
300 saps left on television at the pse or by
faltan 300 saps en teles al pse o para
55 kelvin when we finish the live
55 kelvin cuando terminemos el directo
remind me how tense it is when we go to
recuérdame lo tensa cuando vayamos a
say goodbye I'll send the people to help
despedirnos mando a la gente que ayude
the help of the lordship to arrive okay
la ayuda de la señoría a llegar vale
maduro a little bit he's a little bit
maduro un poquito que es un poquito el
talking he looks this is something that
hablando se mira esto es una cosa que
also happens to many people who have
también pasa muchas la gente que tiene
multiple accounts and it's another thing that
multi cuenta y es otra cosa por la que
I envied the agents no matter angie and
yo envidiaba las agentes no vale angie y
welcome he answers himself
bienvenida se contesta a sí mismo
interacts with himself to position
interactúa con sí mismo para posicionar
the account because because the account doesn't have followers more news abi right now ibai connection with hauran live talking about the subject about the answer of serious eye a bald guy comes out an ass okay okay thanks for letting me know guys those of the group kids info and saving everything in the
chavalería info y guardando todo en el
group please to go commenting the point
grupo por fa para ir comentando lo point
and thank you very much for the psuv
y muchas gracias por el psuv
god do not answer these tender days the
dios no conteste a estos tiernos días el
time interacting with himself and this
tiempo interactuando con sí mismo y esto
is eugenio luz on the youtube account
es eugenio luz en la cuenta de youtube
that we have to talk about an important thing
que hay que hablar una cosa importante
that I already told you yesterday about the
que ya les dije ayer sobre la cuenta de
youtube account the thing the
lo de la cuenta de youtube la cosa
thing of the youtube account
la cosa de la cuenta de youtube
that we will never know the nonsense
que no vamos a saber nunca las burradas
that they will have put out there because  to me
que habrán puesto por ahí porque a mí
with eugenio luz's account he is very
con la cuenta de eugenio luz el muy
pathetic he is very pathetic he put me no if
patético el muy patético me ponía no si
I am not a follower of chocas no or if I
yo no soy seguidor del chocas no o si yo
am not a follower of chocas
no soy seguidor del chocas
I am a follower of javi but I think it is
yo soy seguidor de javi pero me parece
pathetic what he does to xavi with
patético lo que hace a xavi con el
choca I will fall here thank you very much
choque caeré acá muchas gracias
welcome to the family I have to
bienvenido a la familia tengo que
point out one thing that I was telling him
apuntar una cosita que le decía
does that you put them in the video
hace que las metas en el vídeo
with this account he put me in the
con esta cuenta él me ponía a mí en los
comments no I am not a fan of choca
comentarios no yo no soy fan del choque
I am a follower of javi and nevertheless
yo soy seguidor de javi y sin embargo
here I go to what it says
aquí voy a lo que pone
here look choca is a friend of mine in
aquí mira choca es amigo mío en la vida
real life I see him from time to time here in
real lo veo de vez en cuando aquí en
lugo that's why I know what I'm talking about what a
lugo por eso sé de lo que hablo menudo
slap he would give you if I had you in front of me
guantazo te daría si te tuviera delante
him and I
él y yo
look man we will
mira tío
never know all the regrettable things we will
nunca sabremos la de cosas lamentables
that he has written from eugenio's account
que habrá escrito desde la cuenta de
or from the accounts that he has on
eugenio o desde las cuentas que tenga en
youtube we will
youtube
never know
nunca lo sabremos
[Music]
[Música]